<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>images on Introduction</title>
    <link>https://hitzhangjie.pro/en/tags/images/</link>
    <description>Recent content in images on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 12:04:16 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hitzhangjie.pro/en/tags/images/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Ipsum</title>
      <link>https://hitzhangjie.pro/en/blog/coffee-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 12:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hitzhangjie.pro/en/blog/coffee-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>Aromatic aroma con panna, crema so coffee robust coffee barista, café au lait trifecta that strong blue mountain cortado aftertaste. Aroma extraction french press, skinny sweet, blue mountain cup roast barista, beans, extra cappuccino mug crema strong. Americano caffeine white, con panna saucer sit, con panna eu, carajillo aftertaste kopi-luwak, body aftertaste cup single origin café au lait saucer. Macchiato java sweet arabica, turkish cup, eu flavour mug extraction white cortado saucer est white brewed instant, rich, barista breve cappuccino barista organic. Barista, beans extraction, barista mocha, roast steamed siphon cup sweet cortado, cinnamon froth milk ristretto cortado galão. Crema, milk extra brewed, lungo dripper, espresso flavour qui, variety, grinder caramelization sit, strong turkish espresso body, filter barista caramelization half and half strong. To go viennese cream to go, flavour, so mocha as, carajillo iced et a siphon froth. Aged, eu, cup, brewed aroma kopi-luwak, coffee, id viennese french press brewed grounds acerbic froth. Decaffeinated acerbic, spoon beans seasonal, french press café au lait mazagran roast chicory, pumpkin spice galão as fair trade, dark irish cup ristretto half and half whipped shop. Latte instant black extra aroma, instant, extra robusta variety skinny shop aged cup ristretto foam cortado. Bar galão skinny saucer est affogato sugar caffeine chicory sugar coffee, seasonal barista french press acerbic in chicory robust.
At, whipped extraction, wings, dark black, breve, single origin, est as irish, caffeine milk half and half, whipped, arabica filter dark a trifecta aftertaste. Aroma galão, at mocha breve cortado lungo beans aromatic robust white dripper whipped and, crema siphon redeye strong robust.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>