<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Introduction</title>
    <link>https://hitzhangjie.github.io/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 11:58:39 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hitzhangjie.github.io/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hipster Ipsum</title>
      <link>https://hitzhangjie.github.io/en/blog/hipster-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 11:58:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hitzhangjie.github.io/en/blog/hipster-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>Occupy mlkshk kale chips woke, listicle locavore next level fingerstache glossier aesthetic man braid before they sold out kitsch prism. Cred copper mug freegan, flannel YOLO single-origin coffee skateboard artisan four loko church-key man bun. Synth literally gastropub, kombucha chillwave helvetica offal truffaut church-key freegan pop-up gentrify narwhal. Kombucha viral vexillologist green juice. Slow-carb hoodie mumblecore tumeric tattooed meditation, lo-fi fap cred affogato forage whatever austin. Shabby chic direct trade migas, brunch gochujang sriracha chambray fanny pack 8-bit mustache letterpress. Street art umami tattooed, glossier selfies 90&amp;rsquo;s kale chips cred cardigan taxidermy seitan distillery migas.
Chicharrones ethical activated charcoal cardigan vegan copper mug. Ennui messenger bag 90&amp;rsquo;s street art art party etsy. Four loko freegan flannel flexitarian, slow-carb hot chicken vexillologist tote bag church-key tilde pinterest. Ethical hell of retro, mlkshk twee yr selfies asymmetrical venmo. Photo booth mixtape tattooed pop-up, synth flexitarian paleo. DIY cornhole sustainable, gochujang whatever slow-carb hexagon tilde. Bitters XOXO kombucha af.
Organic neutra brooklyn, literally helvetica air plant celiac chia sustainable sriracha. Jean shorts typewriter chambray 90&amp;rsquo;s farm-to-table, man bun tofu VHS. Messenger bag paleo plaid meditation intelligentsia forage, lomo jianbing hell of. Waistcoat synth tacos direct trade truffaut kogi. Gentrify street art woke, everyday carry whatever gastropub PBR&amp;amp;B fixie chambray kale chips af photo booth shoreditch. Thundercats hella cold-pressed, ethical vape irony pitchfork mixtape kombucha heirloom viral hell of deep v banh mi hoodie. Craft beer slow-carb raw denim, ugh asymmetrical artisan banh mi fingerstache trust fund poke bespoke green juice man bun mustache 3 wolf moon.
Seitan tumblr freegan, readymade health goth tofu letterpress mixtape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Ipsum</title>
      <link>https://hitzhangjie.github.io/en/blog/startup-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:04:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hitzhangjie.github.io/en/blog/startup-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>SpaceTeam affordances quantitative vs. qualitative SpaceTeam physical computing earned media thinker-maker-doer pair programming. Bootstrapping pitch deck physical computing driven cortado human-centered design innovate human-centered design driven. Grok pitch deck fund pitch deck sticky note affordances minimum viable product integrate paradigm viral iterate. Driven fund thought leader personas workflow SpaceTeam viral pair programming physical computing intuitive 360 campaign latte bootstrapping minimum viable product. Bootstrapping physical computing responsive pitch deck SpaceTeam parallax long shadow pitch deck bootstrapping ideate.
$ complicated techie code git bash ubuntu &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; return value init foo Responsive innovate grok latte disrupt intuitive actionable insight SpaceTeam grok. Human-centered design Steve Jobs Steve Jobs pitch deck pivot disrupt fund parallax affordances venture capital pair programming. Pivot earned media user centered design affordances agile innovate actionable insight latte.
   this is a table !     this is the 1st row   this is the 2nd row   this is the 3rd row   edgy jo ke lands here   this is the 5th row   this is the 6th row    Waterfall is so 2000 and late personas pitch deck fund big data actionable insight unicorn driven grok. Engaging disrupt ship it big data waterfall is so 2000 and late iterate workflow food-truck pitch deck thought leader. Piverate user centered design unicorn pivot earned media ship it personas moleskine pivot co-working entrepreneur integrate. Affordances actionable insight ship it workflow integrate innovate integrate piverate pivot actionable insight innovate thought leader. Waterfall is so 2000 and late viral viral responsive Steve Jobs driven physical computing thinker-maker-doer piverate pivot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Ipsum</title>
      <link>https://hitzhangjie.github.io/en/blog/coffee-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 12:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hitzhangjie.github.io/en/blog/coffee-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>Aromatic aroma con panna, crema so coffee robust coffee barista, café au lait trifecta that strong blue mountain cortado aftertaste. Aroma extraction french press, skinny sweet, blue mountain cup roast barista, beans, extra cappuccino mug crema strong. Americano caffeine white, con panna saucer sit, con panna eu, carajillo aftertaste kopi-luwak, body aftertaste cup single origin café au lait saucer. Macchiato java sweet arabica, turkish cup, eu flavour mug extraction white cortado saucer est white brewed instant, rich, barista breve cappuccino barista organic. Barista, beans extraction, barista mocha, roast steamed siphon cup sweet cortado, cinnamon froth milk ristretto cortado galão. Crema, milk extra brewed, lungo dripper, espresso flavour qui, variety, grinder caramelization sit, strong turkish espresso body, filter barista caramelization half and half strong. To go viennese cream to go, flavour, so mocha as, carajillo iced et a siphon froth. Aged, eu, cup, brewed aroma kopi-luwak, coffee, id viennese french press brewed grounds acerbic froth. Decaffeinated acerbic, spoon beans seasonal, french press café au lait mazagran roast chicory, pumpkin spice galão as fair trade, dark irish cup ristretto half and half whipped shop. Latte instant black extra aroma, instant, extra robusta variety skinny shop aged cup ristretto foam cortado. Bar galão skinny saucer est affogato sugar caffeine chicory sugar coffee, seasonal barista french press acerbic in chicory robust.
At, whipped extraction, wings, dark black, breve, single origin, est as irish, caffeine milk half and half, whipped, arabica filter dark a trifecta aftertaste. Aroma galão, at mocha breve cortado lungo beans aromatic robust white dripper whipped and, crema siphon redeye strong robust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undated post</title>
      <link>https://hitzhangjie.github.io/en/blog/no-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hitzhangjie.github.io/en/blog/no-date/</guid>
      <description>I was born yesterday, tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>